# Sheila Fundora Galloso

### Computer Science Engineer



- +1 754 610 0521
- Plorida, Miami
- ✓ sheilafundora04@gmail.com
- https://github.com/SheilaFundora
- in www.linkedin.com/in/sheila-fundora

#### **Profile**

Five years since I wrote my first line of code, from that moment I knew I wanted this profession, now I am a Software developer with a frontend profile, with knowledge and skills to develop backend. Focused programmer in developing my ability to overcome learning whatever you propose to me. Passionate about Software Development and good practices.

#### **Skills**

HTML | CSS | JS | TypeScript | GIT

Docker | React | Redux | Next | MUI

PrimeReact | Java | PHP | Python

Django | NodeJS | Express | MYSQL

SQL | PostgresSQL | MariaDB | MongoDB

#### Languages

Spanish | English

#### **Education**

#### Informatic of science University,

Informatic science Engineer 

2018 – 12/2023 | La Habana, Cuba

- Member of the ICPC Caribbean Training Camp.
- (Analysis and design of algorithms).
- Participation in competitive programming contests
- Participation in computer forums, student scientific congresses, computer history forums.
- Member of the jury for the exhibition of works in the scientific congress and history forum

#### **Awards**

- ICPC Caribbean Finals ( Qualifier ) 16th Place in the Caribbean (06/2021)
- ICPC Caribbean Finals 13th Place (07/2021)
- ICPC Caribbean Finals (Qualifier) (03/2022)
- ICPC Caribbean Finals ( Qualifier ) 16th Place in the Caribbean (03/2022)
- Classification for the regional 2022
- 3rd place cup at the faculty level (2022)
- Numerous awards in scientific congresses and history frum at the faculty level and at the university level with excellent results.

#### **Projects**

#### **Cuban Dev Jobs**

06/2022 - 01/2023

Page whose objective is to make life easier for Cuban software developers. We do it by offering employment services, helping you achieve all your employment goals. Committed to helping developers thrive.

#### **Professional Experience**

Fortes, CENTRO DE TECNOLOGÍAS PARA LA FORMACIÓN ☑

02/2022 - 02/2023 | La habana, Cuba

Doing professional internships

- I work with technologies such as PHP, Apache, Python, Django.
- Teamwork on certain tasks in the center, using github.

#### **University of Informatics Sciences Cuba,**

Professor ☑

03/2022 – 07/2022 | La Habana, Cuba Professor of the course "Introduction to Computer Science"

- Professor of practical classes of this subject.
- Jury in the exhibition of all the seminars during the course
- Certificate of appreciation for good work

# Vargas Technology, web development company, $Web\ Developer\ \square$

03/2023 - 11/2023

#### Roles Performed:

- Frontend Developer: Specialized in designing attractive web interfaces.
- Web Designer: Creator of visually impactful experiences.
- Tester: Ensuring quality and performance.

# **Etecsa, Cuban Telecommunications Company S.A,** *Frontend Developer in react* ☑ 09/2023 − 12/2023

Frontend developer for an etecsa Artemisa website, to manage workers' work allowances